[
        {
       "question": "ت و ر و ن ا",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ا م ا د ا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ا ن م ت و",
        "response": "ميناتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك ا ش ا ك ي",
        "response": "كاكاشي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ي و ب ا و",
        "response": "اوبيتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "س ا ر ي س و",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
            {
       "question": "م ا س و ا",
        "response": "اسوما"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر و م ا ش ي ك ا",
        "response": "شيكامارو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن ي و ا",
        "response": "اينو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ج و ي ت ش",
        "response": "تشوجي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن ا ه ي ت ا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن و ش ي",
        "response": "شينو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ب ي ك ا",
        "response": "كيبا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر و ا ب ي م ا غ",
        "response": "غابيمارو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك ي ن ا ك ي",
        "response": "كانيكي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك و ت ا",
        "response": "توكا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك و ك و ر و",
        "response": "كوروكو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ش ي ا ت ي ا",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ف ي ل و",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
            {
       "question": "و ر و ز",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن س ك ا ش",
        "response": "شانكس"
    },
            {
       "question": "س ج ي ن ا",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ا ج ي ر ا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن ا ت س و د ي",
        "response": "تسونادي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ش ي م ا ر و ي ر و ا",
        "response": "اوريتشيمارو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ب س و ا و",
        "response": "اوسوب"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي س ا",
        "response": "ايس"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ي ا",
        "response": "ياتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ن ر ي ا",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
            {
       "question": "ف ا ي ل ي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
            {
       "question": "س ا ك ا م ي",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ن م ر ا",
        "response": "ارمين"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ن و ر ي ا",
        "response": "ايروين"
    },
            {
       "question": "ز ك ي",
        "response": "زيك"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ش و",
        "response": "شوتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن ا م ا ن ي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ج ي و ت",
        "response": "توجي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ب ا ن و ر ا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ج ي و ي",
        "response": "يوجي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ي ت ا د و ا ي",
        "response": "ايتادوري"
    },
            {
       "question": "ج و غ و",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ت و غ",
        "response": "غيتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ه ي م ا",
        "response": "ماهيتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ا س ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن و ي و",
        "response": "يونو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ل و ي ن",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
            {
       "question": "م ي ا ي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ا ر و د ي م",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك و ي د",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ش ا ن ك ا ت",
        "response": "كاتشان"
    },
            {
       "question": "ا و ل ي ت م ا",
        "response": "اول مايت"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن ا س ن ي ف ا",
        "response": "فانيتاس"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك ي م ي ن د و",
        "response": "دومينيك"
    },
            {
       "question": "و ن ي",
        "response": "نوي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ا ل ي",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ا ي ك",
        "response": "كيرا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ل ا",
        "response": "ال"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ي ن",
        "response": "نير"
    },
            {
       "question": "و ر ن ي",
        "response": "نيرو"
    },
            {
       "question": "م ا ش ي ر ا ه",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ب ي س ا ر و",
        "response": "ساروتوبي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ن ب ا",
        "response": "باين"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ا د ي د ا",
        "response": "ديدارا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ا ن ه ي د",
        "response": "هيدان"
    },
            {
       "question": "ز و ك و ك ا",
        "response": "كاكوزو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ي ا م ا",
        "response": "ياماتو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ا ي س",
        "response": "ساي"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ا ك و س ا",
        "response": "ساكورا"
    },
            {
       "question": "م ا ر و ك ا",
        "response": "كوراما"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي ل و م ي ا",
        "response": "ايلومي"
    },
            {
       "question": "س و ه ي ك ا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ي م ي ر و م",
        "response": "ميرويم"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر ا ب ي ك و ك ا",
        "response": "كورابيكا"
    },
            {
       "question": "و ا ك ي ل",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن غ و",
        "response": "غون"
    },
            {
       "question": "ك و غ و",
        "response": "غوكو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ه ا ن غ و",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت ا ج ي ف ي",
        "response": "فيجيتا"
    },
            {
       "question": "م ا ل ب و",
        "response": "بولما"
    },
            {
       "question": "س ك ن ت ر ا",
        "response": "ترانكس"
    },
            {
       "question": "ر و س ي ب",
        "response": "بيروس"
    },
            {
       "question": "ن و ي ز",
        "response": "زينو"
    },
            {
       "question": "ت و ك ا ي",
        "response": "كايتو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ك ي س ا س",
       "response": "ساسكي"
}
      ]